tivocommunity.com 2005-12-11

# Privacy Info

**Terms of Use  
**  
Please read this notice before using our site. By using the site, you agree to abide by these Terms of Use; please do not use our site if you do not agree with the Terms of Use outlined below. AV Science Corporation reserves the right to modify the Terms of Use at its sole discretion, and by using this site, you agree to be bound by the modifications or updates to the Terms of Use.

If you are aged 12 and under,  click here for rules applicable to you. 

 **Privacy Notice  
**  
AV Science/AVS Forum values your privacy. To keep you informed, we have created this privacy statement that discloses our purposes and methods for online collection and use of information. This statement applies to all information collected through the AV Science/AVS Forum websites and information gathered from any web pages that we host. **Site Operator and Contact for Privacy Inquiries:  
**  
AV Science Corporation  
PO BOX 34  
Victor, NY 14564  
585-454-1460  
585-423-8216 [fax]  
Privacy Contact: AV Science/AVS Forum Privacy Administrator  
[privacy@avscience.com](mailto:privacy@avscience.com)  **Types of Information Collected  
**  
Generally, personal information is not collected from visitors to the AV Science/AVS Forum websites. However, in order to access certain special services, personal information is requested; those cases are described in more detail below. **Bulletin Board Registration  
**  
AVS Forum requires a valid e-mail address for users who want to participate in the AVS Forum support forums. This allows us to protect our community from abusive postings and provides a verifiable point of contact should legal questions arise. At any time, you have the ability to keep your e-mail address hidden from other users by selecting that option within your user profile.

Also in the forum registration, you have the option of providing some additional information such as occupation, interests, and homepage URL. This information is made available to other bulletin board users to foster a sense of community. If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave the fields blank and your registration will still be processed.

**_IF YOU ARE 12 YEARS OF AGE OR YOUNGER_** and would like to participate in the AVS Forum Home Theater forums, you will need to print the [ Parental Consent form](http://www.avsforum.com/ubbcgi/ubbmisc.cgi?action=showcoppaform) and have your parent or legal guardian fax it to AV Science at 585-423-8216 prior to posting on the AVS Forum Home Theater forums.

 **Cookies  
**  
Certain activities on the AVS Forum website involve the use of "cookies" to facilitate your experience. This includes retention of your username and password for the AVS Forum and showing a default Topic View when you visit the forums. You have the option to turn these cookies off at any time by updating your user profile preferences. If your browser doesn’t support cookies, or if you have cookies turned off, these preferences will not be set. **Purchasing and/or Credit Card Information  
**  
AV Science/AVS Forum strives to maintain strict security for your private information. Our online ordering pages are SSL 128 bit encryted, providing a secure means of ordering our products. We do not maintain any credit card information at AV Science/AVS Forum, which means that you have to provide it each time you make a purchase, but also means that your information is controlled by you alone. **Disclosure of Personal Information  
**  
AV Science Corporation/AVS Forum, Inc. does not disclose your personally identifying information to any third parties for any purpose without your prior consent unless required by law to do so. All reasonable care is taken by staff handling personal information to ensure its security both offline and online. It is our policy to destroy server access and personal information provided during the technical support process upon completion of the technical support incident.

It’s also important to be aware that when you voluntarily provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a posting on the bulletin board, that information is publicly available and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage the offering of any personally identifying information within the message board itself.

 **Privacy for Children Aged 12 and Under  
**  
Although the AV Science & AVS Forum websites are targeted at a general adult audience, we welcome the participation of younger users with their parents’ consent. We strongly recommend that users 12 and under refrain from offering any personal information either in their user profile or in the message boards themselves, and we encourage parents to stay involved in the online life of their children.

Please view a copy of the [ parental permission form](http://www.avsforum.com/ubbcgi/ubbmisc.cgi?action=showcoppaform). Prior to a child’s registration on the bulletin board, this form must be signed by the child’s parent or legal guardian and faxed to AV Science/AVS Forum at 716-423-8216 or mailed to: 

**AV Science Privacy Administrator,    
AV Science Corporation  
PO BOX 34  
Victor, NY 14564**

AV Science Corporation is prohibited from conditioning a child’s participation in an activity on the child’s disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in such activity.

Parents can review and request deletion of their child’s personal information, and can refuse to permit further collection or use of their child’s information. In order to request such a review, to revoke previously offered parental consent, or to express any concerns regarding a child’s privacy on our website, please send a signed written request to:

**AV Science Corporation  
PO BOX 34  
Victor, NY 14564** **  
or call our Privacy Administrator at 585-454-1460** **Changing or Updating Personal Information  
**  
If you would like to update or change your user profile on the AVS Forum message board,  
just [ click here](http://www.avsforum.com/ubbcgi/ubbmisc.cgi?action=editbio&Browser=&DaysPrune=20&LastLogin=).

If you have questions regarding your information, you can contact our Privacy Administrator at [privacy@avscience.com](mailto:privacy@avscience.com).

 **Here are useful resources for the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. **

Resource Area for the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act 

Effective April 21, 2000, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) seeks to institute online safety measures that protect children aged 12 and under. AVS Forum, as a provider of an online community that are affected by this new law, is providing this resource page to assist its users with understanding this new law.

** Helpful Links:  
**  
How to Comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Rule  

Federal Trade Commission Privacy Initiatives Site (includes link to the full text of the Final Rule)   
[ http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/index.html  
](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/index.html)  
"Children in Cyberspace"  
[ http://www.privacyrights.org/fs/children.htm  
](http://www.privacyrights.org/fs/children.htm)  
CNET article, "Building Websites for Kids; Do: Be Careful with Private Info" (includes link to a "quick fix" privacy policy)  
[ http://www.builder.com/Graphics/Kids/ss03.html  
](http://www.builder.com/Graphics/Kids/ss03.html)  
Online Privacy Alliance's Resources for Business  

**_Thank you....AV Science Inc._**
